<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>windows on Future Insight</title>
    <link>https://future-insight.blog/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in windows on Future Insight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:58:13 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://future-insight.blog/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell: Unleashing the Power of Automation and System Management</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/Power-Shell-Scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 20:58:13 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/Power-Shell-Scripting/</guid>
      <description>Windows, oh Windows! It may look like a friendly playground for beginners, but let me tell you, it&amp;rsquo;s a true powerhouse under the hood, and today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into its secret weapons that every developer should know about!
  Introducing WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux): Ever dreamed of having the best of both worlds? With WSL, you can seamlessly run a full-fledged Linux environment right inside your Windows system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winget: A Powerful Tool for Effortless Software Installation on Windows</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/winget-package-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:51:13 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/winget-package-manager/</guid>
      <description>For years, when it came to installing applications on Windows, we would visit the internet, like the Google Chrome website, and download the .exe file. Once downloaded, we would click and click until the application was installed on our system.
However, this method had its drawbacks. If you had a slow internet connection, it would take time to download all the exe files from the browser, and then you had to go through the clicking process to install each application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Sub-System for Linux (WSL)</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/wsl-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 23:04:42 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/wsl-install/</guid>
      <description>Linux is ubiquitous, and no matter how much we resist, there will come a point when we must embrace it. So, why not start now? In this article, we will explore the process of installing Linux on Windows.
As we embark on this journey, you may find yourself pondering various questions, such as:
 What is WSL? What is WSL2? What sets WSL and WSL2 apart? Why do I need WSL?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Security: Protecting Your Operating System</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/secure-your-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:58:06 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/OS/windows/secure-your-windows/</guid>
      <description>The world is changing rapidly. With the rise of AI and advancements in computing power, establishing a secure internet connection has become increasingly challenging. The vastness of the internet allows for access to a wide range of information, but it also poses risks. If one is not cautious, personal information can be sold online. Various organizations track your online activities, creating profiles that are used to deliver targeted advertisements. Additionally, the threat of viruses looms, capable of compromising your system and resulting in the loss of valuable data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
