<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Future Insight</title>
    <link>https://future-insight.blog/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Future Insight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:21:08 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://future-insight.blog/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Scrapper</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/web-scrapper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:21:08 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/web-scrapper/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Implementation: Conclusion: Contact Me: If you have any questions, please contact me
 Email My website GitHub  I will see you next time❤️.
References: Here are all of the links and references that I used to write this blog, so feel free to visit them to get some more help.
Articles references:  Article 1 Article 2 Article 3  GitHub Repository:  GitHub Repository 1 GitHub Repository 2 GitHub Repository 3  Video References:  Video Reference 1 Video Reference 2 Video Reference 3  Thumbnail: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Assistant</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/Parking-Assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:03:36 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/Parking-Assistant/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In this project we are going to make a parking assistant. Using the power of IOT Devices we will be able to detect the parking space, Also we reserved the parking space.
Technology Used: The project is developed using the following technologies:
 HTML CSS JavaScript Bootstrap  Required Software: To run this application on your computer you need to install the following software:
 Xampp Node JS VS Code Arduino IDE  Required Hardware: For this application to run properly we also required hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://future-insight.blog/Project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:03:15 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.blog/Project/</guid>
      <description>Projects  Parking Assistant | 3rd Augest 2022
 Using the power of IOT Devices Software, me and my team created this project to detect different parking spaces in a specific area. The use cases of this Porject are limitless, eg: Use this project with hardware to detect different things in a specific area.   React Porofilo Website | 2nd February 2023
 Using React to create a stunning Porofilo project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
