<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>new-tech on Future Insight</title>
    <link>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tags/new-tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in new-tech on Future Insight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:00:34 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://future-insight.netlify.app/tags/new-tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flutter Kickstart: From Setup to Emulator in Style</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/flutter-kickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:00:34 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/flutter-kickstart/</guid>
      <description>I must say that setting up Flutter is not easy. There are a lot of videos out there that claim to help you set up the Flutter SDK for Windows, Linux, or macOS, but they are often incomplete and don&amp;rsquo;t answer the most basic questions you may have. So, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write this blog to help you guys out.
From day one, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a web developer, using React, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter: Dart Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/dart-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 14:07:01 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/dart-programming/</guid>
      <description>I want to learn Flutter and make cool apps, but it was a while ago that I had to learn a new Programming language, and I am rusty to learn a new programming language, but I am eager to learn something new, so in this blog post, I will be learning the Dart Programming language, and I will be sharing my experience with you guys.
Before we begin, we need dark sdk on my system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Journey Insights: Flutter Begining</title>
      <link>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/Flutter-begining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 22:49:13 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://future-insight.netlify.app/tech-journey/Flutter/Flutter-begining/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Hugo for a while, and I have created this website to blog, but things have changed, and I want to expand it and make it more than just a blog. I want to make it a place where people can come and learn new things. So I have decided to start a new series of blogs where I will be learning new technologies and sharing my experiences with you guys.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
